var questions = [
    {
        Question: "Which of these rivers runs through the French City of Perpignan?",
        Answers: ['Têt', 'Loire', 'Seine', 'Cam'],
        Correct: 'Têt'
    },
    {
        Question: "Which Country has the Highest Number of Pyramids?",
        Answers: ['Egypt', 'Mexico', 'Sudan', 'Peru'],
        Correct: 'Sudan'
    },
    {
        Question: "Which Country has the Longest Coastline in the World?",
        Answers: ['Canada', 'United States of America', 'Australia', 'Greenland'],
        Correct: 'Canada'
    },
    {
        Question: "Which is the Newest Country in the World?",
        Answers: ['East Timor', 'South Sudan', 'Montenegro', 'Palau'],
        Correct: 'South Sudan'
    },
    {
        Question: "Which of these Countries has 3 Capital Cities?",
        Answers: ['United States of America', 'South Africa', 'Russia', 'Turkey'],
        Correct: 'South Africa'
    },
    {
        Question: "Which European Country Borders the Highest Number of Other Countries?",
        Answers: ['Romania', 'Germany', 'France', 'Hungary'],
        Correct: 'Germany'
    },
    {
        Question: "Which City has the 25th Largest Metropolitan Population in France (2017)?",
        Answers: ['Brest', 'Dijon', 'Perpignan', 'Le Havre'],
        Correct: 'Dijon'
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the Second Largest City in the UK?",
        Answers: ['Manchester', 'Edinburgh', 'Birmingham', 'Liverpool'],
        Correct: 'Birmingham'
    },
    {
        Question: "Montmartre is a Neighbourhood in Which City?",
        Answers: ['Montreal', 'Paris', 'Geneva', 'Cambridge'],
        Correct: 'Paris'
    },
    {
        Question: "Which South American Country has Borders with 10 other Countries?",
        Answers: ['Argentina', 'Paraguay', 'Bolivia', 'Brazil'],
        Correct: 'Brazil'
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the Largest Desert in the World? ",
        Answers: ['Gobi', 'Antarctic', 'Arctic', 'Sahara'],
        Correct: 'Antarctic'
    },
    {
        Question: "The Smallest Country in the World(by size) is ...",
        Answers: ['Vatican City', 'Monaco', 'San Marino', 'Liechtenstein'],
        Correct: 'Vatican City'
    },
    {
        Question: "Which City has the Highest Population Density?",
        Answers: ['Jakarta, Indonesia', 'Mexico City, Mexico', 'Seoul, South Korea', 'Manilla, Philippines'],
        Correct: 'Manilla, Philippines'
    }



]
